ultimateteam.co.uk 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy - FIFA 19 Ultimate Team, FUT Web App, Beta & Demo

**Overview**

This website privacy policy describes how UltimateTeamUK protects and makes use of the information provided to us when individuals use this website.

If you are asked to provide any information when using this website, it will be described within this privacy policy.

We will always try to ensure that this privacy policy is up-to-date.

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please email [enquiries@ultimateteam.co.uk](mailto:enquiries@ultimateteam.co.uk)

 **Introduction**

The information collected from our readers is for the sole purpose of enabling the proper functioning of this website. We also collect information to better understand how visitors use this website.

 **What information do we collect?**

  * Name (comments & newsletters)
  * Email address (comments & newsletters)
  * Demographic information
  * Website usage data
  * Other information relevant to enquiries

 **How do we use this data?**

  * For our own internal records
  * To improve the products and services we provide
  * To contact you in response to a specific enquiry
  * To customise the website for you
  * To send you emails regarding up-to-date FUT content and offers you may be interested in

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a small file placed on your computer’s hard drive. It enables our website to identify your computer as you view different pages on our website.

Cookies allow websites and applications to store your preferences in order to present content, options and functions that are specific to you. They also enable us to see information such as what pages are being visited and the length of time on our website.

 **How we use cookies**

  * Analyse our web traffic using analytics packages
  * Test content on our website
  * Store information about your preferences
  * To recognise you when you return to our website

Cookies do not give us access to your computer or information about you, other than what you choose to share with us.

 **Controlling cookies**

You can use your web browser’s cookie settings to determine how our website uses cookies. If you do not want our website to store cookies on your computer or device, you should set your web browser to refuse cookies.

Please note that doing this may affect how our website functions and some of the advertisements personalised for you.

Unless you have changed your cookie settings, our website will store cookies when you visit.

 **Security**

Your security is of paramount importance to us. We will always hold your information securely. We will never sell or share your information to third-parties without consent.

 **Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites. We have no control over how these websites operate and therefore always be careful when choosing to submit information to these websites.
